Okay, what up y'all? We're back with a
brand new video. Make sure you like and
subscribe if you appreciate the content.
Today, we are going over the Min Max
image generation workflow. With this,
you'll be able to basically just upload
your references and you'll be able to
get,
you know, a mashup of your references in
whatever setting you prompted for. So, I
think it's pretty interesting for the
people who don't want to train Laura's
and everything every time. I think this
could be an option. It's not going to
work every time, though. It's pretty
consistent, but I would say it's like
90%, 85% maybe.
So, yeah, that's pretty much it. I'll go
over the workflow. It's nothing too
complex.
The most important part is going to be
the prompting, obviously. Because Min
Max does require certain type of
prompting to give you the best possible
results. So, um
I already released my
prompting LM Studio custom node to my
subscribers. You don't need the node to
actually, you know, get good results,
but I would say it does help with the
efficiency of the workflow. So, if you
want to grab that, make sure you sub.
It's only 12 bucks and you get so much
more than just the node. You get
workflows, you get
other custom nodes and everything. So,
[music]
Now that I said that, let's go over the
actual workflow. So, here
we load the models, nothing too crazy.
We use an FL2A and Ref2V [music]
A
hybrid model. So, this model can
basically do both
image [music] and text to video and
reference to video. So, that basically
just
lets you use one model instead of, you
know, switching between multiple models.
Then we use say your tension. If you
don't have it installed,
I would highly recommend that you do
that. If you don't know how, um, I might
make a video on how to install Segi
Tension using AI agents and stuff.
You're not going to have to do anything.
You just prompt for it, basically.
And yeah, so here
we use a eight-step Laura for the
workflow.
The reason [music] why is that,
while we could do 40 and 50 [music]
steps, I think the eight steps result is
pretty good for what it is. So
you can do as many steps as you want,
really.
Doesn't really matter, but just make
sure that you match your Laura to what
you're doing, right? Um
And then, if we go over here with this,
we just leave as is. We don't really
play with the audio in this model, in
this workflow. We do need to load it,
but we're not really using it because
we're generating one frame. Um,
>> [music]
>> and here, this is going to be another
custom node I made. You don't need to
use that, um, but you basically can just
choose the megapixel resolution of your
generation.
Yeah, you pass the resolution values to
the empty latent image, which goes
directly inside
the
sampler.
It's only one frame. You don't need to
generate five frames and then crazy
weird You just need one frame.
Um, so yeah, and then over here, we're
going to have the reference loader.
>> [music]
>> So, this is a node I made, like I said.
You can just click over here and select
your references.
Okay, so we have all our references
loaded.
We can just run it right now.
And what's going to happen? So, we
basically send all our images and the
prompt directly to Kwen 3.8 27B
obliterated, which is basically the
uncensored version of the model.
But for the model, the LLM, you can use
whatever um
whatever model works on your PC.
Obviously, uh I would recommend that you
unload the model after it's done uh
doing the prompting. Uh with the node, I
added this over here, so you can just uh
check that and it will unload it
directly. Uh
if you don't have the node, you just
need to go in LM Studio and basically
unload the thing uh by yourself.
So, you load it and then you unload it.
Um but, yeah, super easy. Um
and then it goes through um
this node over here and we get the final
result over here, okay? Uh
as we can see, I think it's that's a
pretty good result.
Uh we got the face, we got the body with
the the outfit, and we got uh
the exact room we asked for.
Um so, yeah, I think that's a pretty
good result. What we can do here and
just try something else. So, we can try
another body type, another outfit.
Let's just try something else.
Um
Let's try that, okay? So, what we're
going to say is uh we still use image
four. So, image four is going to be the
environment this time.
Um image two is going to be the body
only.
And image three is going to be uh the
clothing. So, use image three for the
clothing.
And we send that to the LLM and let's
see what we get.
And this is basically like a jacket. If
it wasn't clear, that's a jacket, right?
Okay.
Okay, so we got the final result. Um
what do you guys think? I mean, I think
it's okay. I think it's not that bad. Um
>> [music]
>> obviously, the body type, I mean, we
can't really see much, which uh is
uh you know, kind of expected with a
jacket like that.
So, yeah. That's that's kind of the
workflow.
Obviously, the final result is not going
to be the most sharp thing you ever got
in your life, okay? So, what I would
recommend is that you run um
your final image in my upscaling
workflow
or you if you have your own upscaling
workflow, we can use that.
Um and you can just, you know,
rerun your image as a low D noise and
you should be good to go. High
resolution image with exactly what you
asked for.
If you need a consistent room, you can
use this workflow as well.
I made a multiple examples on my school
page. So, if you want to see the exact
results, you can go over there and just
grab that.
And yeah, that's pretty much it, guys.
Appreciate the support always. Make sure
you sub on school and I will see you in
the next one. I will be making a video
on how to install LM Studio and all that
stuff
and the sage attention stuff as well.
Cuz I know a lot of people do need to um
install this stuff. So, that's pretty
much it. I'll see you in the next one.
Peace.